<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<unit xmlns="http://www.sdml.info/srcML/src" language="Java"
      filename="D:\bio\git\biorimp\BIO-RIMP\test_data\code\acra\src\main\java\org\acra\ReportingInteractionMode.java">
    <comment type="block">/*
        * Copyright 2010 Emmanuel Astier &amp; Kevin Gaudin
        *
        * Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
        * you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
        * You may obtain a copy of the License at
        *
        * http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
        *
        * Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
        * distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
        * WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
        * See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
        * limitations under the License.
        */
    </comment>
    <package>package
        <name><name>org</name>.
            <name>acra</name>
        </name>
        ;
    </package>

    <comment type="javadoc">/**
        * Defines the different user interaction modes for ACRA.
        * &lt;ul&gt;
        * &lt;li&gt;SILENT: No interaction, reports are sent silently and a "Force close"
        * dialog terminates the app.&lt;/li&gt;
        * &lt;li&gt;TOAST: A simple Toast is triggered when the application crashes, the
        * Force close dialog is not displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
        * &lt;li&gt;NOTIFICATION: A status bar notification is triggered when the application
        * crashes, the Force close dialog is not displayed. When the user selects the
        * notification, a dialog is displayed asking him if he is ok to send a report&lt;/li&gt;
        * &lt;/ul&gt;
        */
    </comment>
    <enum>
        <specifier>public</specifier>
        enum <name>ReportingInteractionMode</name>
        <block>{
            <comment type="javadoc">/**
                * No interaction, reports are sent silently and a "Force close" dialog
                * terminates the app.
                */
            </comment>
            <expr>
                <name>SILENT</name>
            </expr>
            ,
            <comment type="javadoc">/**
                * A status bar notification is triggered when the application crashes, the
                * Force close dialog is not displayed. When the user selects the
                * notification, a dialog is displayed asking him if he is ok to send a
                * report.
                */
            </comment>
            <expr>
                <name>NOTIFICATION</name>
            </expr>
            ,
            <comment type="javadoc">/**
                * A simple Toast is triggered when the application crashes, the Force close
                * dialog is not displayed.
                */
            </comment>
            <expr>
                <name>TOAST</name>
            </expr>
            ,
            <comment type="javadoc">/**
                * Direct dialog: a report confirmation dialog is displayed right after the crash.
                * Will replace {@link #NOTIFICATION} mode.
                */
            </comment>
            <expr>
                <name>DIALOG</name>
            </expr>
            }
        </block>
    </enum>
</unit>
